Mss.B.G61
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1901-1965
  - Jennings, Ralph D., November, 1951
  - The Jersey Bulletin, January 26, 1932
  - Johns-Manville, Inc., November 26, 1924
  - Johnson, Edward C., August, 1927
  - Johnson, Emil R., 1931-1943
  - Johnson, Fred, February 12, 1929
  - Johnson, Howard D., April, 1941
  - Jolliffe, C.B., 1927
  - Jolly, James, April, 1928
  - Jones, C.E., February 3, 1944
  - Jones, D.F., Nov. 21, 1924
  - Jones, Merle C., March 3, 1953
  - Jones, Roy E., 1927-1931
  - Jordon, James, April 20, 1932
  - Joshi, P.N., December 8, 1937
  - Juhn, Mary, November 5, 1952
  - Jull, Morley A., 1923-1959
  - Kaempffert, Waldemar Bernhard, September, 1941
  - Kallmann, Franz J., 1947
  - Keeler, Clyde Edgar, 1930-1941
  - Kempster, H.L., August 9, 1954
  - Kendall, J.C., 1930
  - Kendrick, J.F., August 2, 1937
  - Kennard, D.C., 1926-1934
  - Kennard, L.V., August 10, 1933
  - Kennedy, Robert, January 5, 1967
  - Kernahan, John P., 1925-1926
  - Kerr, W.S., 1931
  - Keyes-Davis Company, Inc., January 23, 1923
  - Keystone State Caviary, September 30, 1932
  - Kiesselbach, T.A., 1922
    Scope and Contents note
    Corn investigations.
  - Kilgore, Harley Martin, 1943
  - Kimball, Elliot, 1950-1951
  - Kimber, John E., 1928-1964
  - King, Helen Dean, February 20, 1948
  - King, J.D., 1935
  - King, J.W.B., Undated
  - King, John F., September 30, 1941
  - Kirkpatrick, William F., 1926-1931
  - Klein, G.T., 1935-1953
  - Knaudel, H.C., February 6, 1929
  - Knauth, Oswald W., December 11, 1935
    See also: Century Association, in:
  - Knower, Henry, April 3, 1911
  - Knowlton, Frank L., August 24, 1927
  - Koppers Products Company, July, 1932
  - Krediet, G., August 14, 1930
  - Kummerloeve, Hans, 1930
    Comparative investigations of the gonad system of female birds.
  - Kurdt, Albert, December 29, 1934
  - Kyle, W.A., 1930
  - Kyle, Wendell H., 1942-1964
  - Lackey, Susan Jane, June 7, 1954
  - Lake, E.R., February 26, 1925
  - LaMaster, J.P., 1932
  - Lamb, Leland W., 1941-1964
  - Lambert, H.T., 1931-1932
  - Lambert, W.V., 1928, 1941
  - Lamoreux, W.F., 1944, 1946
  - Lamson, G.H., Jr., December 31, 1925
  - Landauer, Walter, 1929-1949
  - Landers, Frary, & Clark, November 9, 1928
  - Landis, Carney, October 18, 1947
  - Langmead, Peter, 1950
  - Lantz, James L., November 11, 1925
  - Larionson, W., 1929
  - Larrabee, Edward N., 1929-1948
  - Lash, David C., 1932
  - Laughlin, Harry Hamilton, 1927-1932
  - Lawson, G.L., 1924-1926
  - Lebedeff, Gabriel A., 1928
  - Leckie, J.N., October, 1931
  - Lee, C.D., October 2, 1941
  - Lee, Clarence E., 1948-1951
  - Lee, Montrose, March 17, 1924
  - Leisner, Robert S., October 21, 1963
    See: American Institute of Biological Sciences - Visiting Biologists Program, in:
  - Lentz, John B., 1927-1933
  - Leonard, Samuel L., 1936
  - Leppert, Charles H., Company, May, 1930
  - Lerner, Isadore Michael, 1952
  - Levy, David M., 1933-1934
  - Lewis, E.B., 1962
  - Lewis, Edward M., March, 1930
  - Lewis, John G., December 4, 1928
  - Libby, Benjamin F., 1923-1927
  - Liljeberg, Armas, 1932
  - Lindsey, A.W., November, 1931
  - Lindsley, V.T., May 5, 1925
  - Linton, Ralph, September, 1949
  - Lipman, Jacob G., April 3, 1923
  - Lippincott, William A., 1923-1928
  - Lipschutz, Alexander, 1924
  - Literary Digest, 1926, 1934
  - Little, Clarence Cook, 1924-1948
  - Little, Stuart L., January 10, 1925
  - Lloyd, E.A., 1927
  - Locke, J.B., March 4, 1927
  - Locke, W.T., 1931
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., May 3, 1943
  - Loeb, Leo, 1925-1942
  - Lounsbury, Lincoln R., 1926-1932
  - Lovejoy, Frank W., June 1932
  - Lovell, C., April 28, 1931
  - Lovell, E.C., May 6, 1931
  - Lukacs, H.E., 1938
  - Lund, Charles G., December, 1928
  - Lunn, Alfred G., 1926-1935
  - Lush, Jay Laurence, 1932-1938
  - Lutz, ---, July 19, 1912
  - McAlpin Hotel, November 14, 1928
  - MacArthur, Kenneth C., May 8, 1953
  - MacArthur, R.J., 1942-1944
  - McCarry, Miles R., March 14, 1952
  - McCay, C.M., March 12, 1951
    See also: Journal of Experimental Medicine, Kertesz, Z. I., in:
  - McCollum, E.V., April 15, 1929
  - McCook, Anson T., 1930
  - McDowell, J.C., April 23, 1931
  - McGill, Thomas, January 16, 1964
  - Mack, M.J., 1928
  - McKissick, Harvey, August 5, 1925
  - Macleod, J.N., 1931
  - McMahan, A.B., April 16, 1925
  - McMullen, Darwin, March 9, 1942
  - McPhee, Hugh C., July 18, 1935
  - McRae, H.R., 1930
  - Madsen, Karl, 1930
  - Magoon, C.H., October, 1932
  - Mahoney, Thomas, 1956
  - Mallock, Walter Scott, April 11, 1934
  - Malone, Edward F., March 6, 1923
  - Mancini, L. Phillip, June 6, 1942
  - Mandeville, Paul, February 28, 1936
  - Mangelsdorf, Paul C., 1951
  - Marble, D.R., 1933, 1941
  - Marchant Calculating Machine Company, December, 1931
  - Mariappan, P., Undated
  - Marquardt, J.C., July 10, 1934
  - Marshak, Alfred George, April 6, 1937
  - Marshall, Charles E., May 23, 1925
  - Marshall, F.H.A., November 8, 1921
  - Martens, Henry L., November, 1952
  - Martin, J. Holmes, 1926-1958
  - Martin, J.T., Jr., May, 1932
  - Mason, C. Russell, September, 1948
  - Mason, Irving, 1942
  - Massachusetts Agriculture College, 1927-1931
  - Matsuda, Yoko, 1926-1927
  - Mattson, Ivar, October 30, 1925
  - Maw, A.J.G., November, 1943
  - Maw, W.A., 1932
  - May, H.G., 1926
  - Mayhew, Roy L., August, 1931
  - Maynard, R.S., 1932-1948
  - [Mead?], Charlie, November 17, 1907
  - Medina, Hugo, June 26, 1930
  - Mehrhof, Norman R., July 5, 1929
  - Meredith, W.O.S., 1941
  - Merrill, M.C., June 22, 1926
  - Meyer, O. Jackson, Jr., October 20, 1936
  - Meyerhoff, Howard A., March 10, 1953
  - Middlebury College, February 9, 1931
  - Miles, Garry A., August 17, 1936
  - Miller, A.W., April, 1936
  - Miller, Amos C., October 21, 1935
  - Miller, Gerrit Smith, August 19, 1941
  - Miller, Raymond J., December 13, 1926
  - Miller, Wilbur H., 1927-1928
  - Mills, Clarence A., October 3, 1949
  - Mitchell, Frank E., December 21, 1929
  - Mitchell, H.H., October 29, 1924
  - Moffett, W.K., April, 1931
  - Monahan, William C., 1923-1928
  - Monroe Calculating Machine Company, Inc., September 11, 1928
  - Montgomery, R.L., January 30, 1936
  - Montgomery Ward & Company, 1928
  - Moore, John C., Corporation, 1927-1931
  - Moore Brothers Corporation of Albany, July 3, 1936
  - Moreland, Wallace S., September 13, 1928
  - Morgan, Ann, 1925-1929
  - Morgan, Thomas Hunt, 1907-1928
  - Morgan, Walter C, Jr., 1953
  - Morris, Lawrence, March, 1942
  - Morse, Undated
  - Morse, E.W., Jr., August 17, 1936
  - Morse, Luther E., January 24, 1928
  - Moulton, James M., November 17, 1952
  - Moulton, L.H., February 22, 1937
  - Moultrie, Fred, 1966
  - Mueller, Clyde D., 1952
  - Mueller, William S., 1931-1932
  - Muller, Hermann Joseph, 1965
  - Muniandi, ---, November 4, 1964
  - Munro, S.S., 1931-1943
  - Murphy, James B., 1925
  - Mussehl, F.E., 1925-1927
  - Nass, Ewald, 1951
  - National Audubon Society, September 14, 1953
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ in the U.S.A., April 2, 1953
  - National Poultry Council, June 5, 1930
  - National Research Council, 1923, 1930
  - Nevalonnyj, M., 1930-1931
  - New England Laboratories, June 22, 1927
  - New England Poultryman, July, 1931
  - New Jersey Agricultural Experiment Station, September 2, 1933
  - New Jersey State Poultry Association, 1949
  - New York Academy of Sciences, March 18, 1957
  - New York Guernsey Breeder's Cooperative, December 21, 1934
  - New York State Tri-County Poultrymen's Meeting, October 18, 1933
  - Nisbet, J.S., August 25, 1941
  - Nodine, Earle H., October 10, 1927
  - Nonidez, José F., 1923-1928
  - Nordby, J.E., February, 1930
  - Nordskog, A.W., May, 1963
  - Norris, L.C., February 2, 1929
  - Norton, H.W., Jr., 1930-1935
  - Noss, Samuel, October, 1928
  - Noyes, H.V., May 14, 1934
  - Nutter, Albert, January 26, 1943
  - Ober, Frank W., 1930-1935
  - Oberkamper, Ivan, 1932
  - O'Conner, Robert B., 1932
  - Ogilby, R.R., November 14, 1927
  - O'Harrig, Jose, Jr., September, 1954
  - Ohio State University, June 22, 1929
  - Onion, Leonard W., 1924-1926
  - Palmer, L.S., 1927
  - Palmer, T.S., July, 1930
  - Papadopoulos, P.L., November 10, 1931
  - Papanicolaou, George N., Jr., 1930
  - Pappenheimer, Alwin M., 1925-1928
  - Parker, R.R., August 17, 1925
  - Parkhurst, Raymond T., 1929-1944
  - Parkhurst, Robert B., December 4, 1928
  - Patch, E.L., Company, 1924-1925
  - Patton, John W., July 10, 1925
  - Payne, Fernandus, 1939-1951
  - Payne, George Henry, November 1, 1926
  - Payne, Loyal F., 1923-1963
  - Pearl, Raymond, 1909-1931
  - Pease, Richard, July 19, 1933
  - Peaslee, Charles E., 1924-1925
  - Peelle, William R., March 4, 1953
  - Pejouhy, R.A., 1932-1933
  - Penney, J.C., September 18, 1942
  - Perry, Clay, 1944
  - Petersime Incubator Company, February 15, 1951
  - Peterson, Guy A., 1948
  - Phillips, M.T., July 2, 1932
  - Philpott, Denis, June, 1930
  - Pike, Oliver G., 1932
  - Pilla, Remo, March 13, 1933
  - Pincus, J.W., 1931
  - Pinkum, Daniel, 1932
  - Plain, Frank A., February 1, 1929
  - Plank, G.M. van der, September 22, 1930
  - Plata Guerrero, Roberto, September 21, 1944
  - Plough, Harold H., 1936-1937
  - Plum, Mogens, September 5, 1934
  - Pohle, Ernst A., February 14, 1927
  - Poole, Harry, 1942-1944
  - Popenoe, Paul, 1932
    Contains pamphlet "Human Sterilization".
  - Popular Science Monthly, 1925, 1930
    See also: Youmans, W.J., in:
  - Port Morris Tool and Machine Company, 1931
  - Poultry Science Association, 1928-1932
    See also: Martin, J Holmes, in:
  - Poultry World, April 25, 1938
  - Pratt Food Company, January 2, 1925
  - Prentice, Alta Rockefeller, 1953-1958
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #1, 1922-1923
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #2, 1924-1927
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #3, 1928-1929
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #4, 1930-1931
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #5, 1932-1933
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #6, 1934
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #7, 1935-1936
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #8, 1937-1941
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #9, 1942-1943
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #10, 1948-1949
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #11, January-May 1950
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #12, June-December 1950
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #13, 1951
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee #14, 1952-1953
  - Prentice, J. Rockefeller #1, 1930-1937
  - Prentice, J. Rockefeller #2, 1938
    See also: Dunn Harland K., in:
  - Prentice, J. Rockefeller #3, 1939-1940
  - Prentice, J. Rockefeller #4, 1949-1953
  - Prentice, J. Rockefeller #5, 1954-1964
  - Prentice, J. Rockefeller #6, 1965
  - Prescott, M.S., July 26, 1932
  - Priebe, Frank, Undated
  - Purdue University, August 6, 1928
  - Purina Mills, 1934
  - Pushee, George, October 27, 1931
  - Rada, Norman J., March 26, 1930
  - Radi, M.H., August 9, 1935
  - Ragsdale, A.C., 1926, 1928
  - Ramp, Mrs. W.C., January 24, 1936
  - Ramsay, M.J., May, 1932
  - Rand, Frederick V., September 28, 1926
  - Rand, Jessie, 1926-1927
  - Reed, G.W., April, 1932
  - Reliable Poultry Journal, 1926-1929
  - Rhoades, Ernest, 1926-1927
  - Rice, Edward L., June 23, 1928
  - Rice, James E., July 18, 1934
  - Rice, V.A., 1928-1932
  - Richardson, H.L., 1933-1935
  - Richardson, R.B., January 28, 1937
  - Ricker, Earl M., 1931
  - Riddle, Oscar, 1926-1933
  - Ritzman, Ernest George, 1932-1936
  - Robb, W.J., April 18, 1925
  - Roberts, E., 1925-1951
  - Robbins, Frank Egleston, June 21, 1928
  - Roberts, Nelson A., 1924-1942
  - Robertson, Forbes W., 1952
  - Robinson, Mrs. Marie, 1953, 1955
  - Robinson, W.L., 1951
  - Rollins, W.C., 1954
  - Romanoff, Alexis L., 1932
  - Ronald Press Company, June 18, 1948
    See also: Dobzhansky, Theodosius G., in:
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas G., May 4, 1933
  - Roper, Elmo, November 23, 1948
  - Ross, S.M., 1930
  - Roux, L.L., August 9, 1955
  - Rowe, Allen Winter, 1930
  - Rowe, Clyde F., December 20, 1935
  - Rowell, Homer R., April 3, 1934
  - Ruggles, Arthur H., December 31, 1923
  - Rumely, Edward A., January 4, 1952
    See also: Rand, James H., Jr., in:
  - Rundquist, E.A., 1948
  - Runner, Meredith, 1948-1952
    See also: Jackson, Roscoe B., Memorial Laboratory, in:
  - Rural New Yorker, June 9, 1934
  - Russell, E.S., 1925
  - Russell, James E., 1932
  - Russell, W.L., May 25, 1948
  - Ryan, John J., April 3, 1925
  - Ryan, William E., Jr., March 11, 1929
  - Saint John, R.R., February 23, 1944
  - Salisbury, S.M., 1924, 1931
  - Salmon, H.L., December 7, 1926
  - Sanborn, Herbert, September 8, 1944
  - Sanborn, L.D., 1943
  - Sanborn, Ruby, 1923-1930
  - Sanctuary, W.C., 1924-1949
  - Sandberg, H., May 4, 1931
  - Sander, H.G.F., 1947
  - Sanders, J., 1932
  - Sandnes, Gunnar, March 4, 1942
  - Savage, E.S., September 17, 1934
  - Sawin, Paul B., December, 1952
  - Sax, Karl, 1952
  - Scales, F.M., 1931
  - Schaible, Louis D., 1930-1932
  - Schlemmer, W.C., 1926
  - Schneider, H., March 8, 1947
  - Schwenker, Victor, 1949-1953
  - Science, 1933-1954
  - Science Illustrated, October 5, 1948
  - Science League of America, May 1, 1925
  - Science Service, 1949
  - Scientific American, 1949, 1951, 1966
  - Scott, George G, 1928, 1941
  - Scott, James F., 1929, 1931
  - Scott, Thomas, 1929-1934
  - Second International Congress for Sex Research, 1930
  - Sherman, H.C., January 18, 1924
  - Shoffner, Robert N., August, 1964
  - Shufelt, Clinton F., December 4, 1948
  - Shull, Aaron Franklin, January 3, 1922
  - Shull, George Harrison, 1922-1933
  - Sibley, John, 1931
  - Sievers, F.J., 1931
  - Simonnet, E., Undated
  - Simons, J.H., May 3, 1943
  - Singleton, W. Ralph, 1952
  - Sinnott, Edmund Ware, January 18, 1929
  - Sixth International Congress of Genetics, 1929-1930
  - Skaller, F., May 31, 1948
  - Skarman, Sven, September 22, 1936
  - Skidmore, D.E., November 14, 1929
  - Slater, Duane S., May, 1928
  - Slater, W.K., January 3, 1930
  - Smiley, H.J., 1941-1942
  - Smith, A.C., July 27, 1925
  - Smith, A.W., May 31, 1934
  - Smith, C.A., November, 1931
  - Smith, Carleton G., 1931?
  - Smith, Edgar C., March 22, 1926
  - Smith, Erwin Frink, June 22, 1925
  - Smith, Geoffrey, Undated
  - Smith, George P., 1929-1932
  - Smith, H.D., 1926
  - Smith, J. Russell, 1951
  - Smith, Leslie R., January 14, 1925
  - Smith, Philip E., August 1, 1934
  - Smith, Theobald, 1923-1932
  - Smyth, J.R., 1933
  - Smyth, J. Robert, Jr., 1952, 1964
  - Snell, George Davis, December, 1951
  - Souquet, F., 1923-1935
  - Southeastern egg laying contest, December 22, 1925
  - Southern California Farm Bureau egg laying contest, Undated
  - Spence, William J., 1933-1934
  - Spencer Chemical Company, March 4, 1953
  - Spillman, William Jasper, 1909-1911
  - Spotts, George R., April 18, 1953
  - Standard Oil Company, March 20, 1950
  - State University of Iowa, February, 1931
  - Stebbins, G. Ledyard, Jr., 1952
  - Steckley, Vern F., June, 1950
  - Steele, Dewey G., May, 1937
  - Steele, J.A., 1934-1935
  - Steelman, L.W., 1924
  - Stern, Curt, September, 1949
  - Stewart, Lloyd L., 1925-1927
  - Stockard, Charles Rupert, 1927, 1937
  - Stockbridge, Robert R., May 17, 1944
  - Stone, Benjamin C., August 25, 1943
  - Storer, John H, Jr., 1927-1935
  - Stratton, Eugene C., May 10, 1934
  - Strong, Leonell C., 1932-1934
  - Strong, Reuben Myron, 1926-1927
  - Strong, Mrs. Richard W., March 5, 1942
  - Stubbs, E.L., November 16, 1933
  - Sturm, Ernest, Undated
  - Sturtevant, Alfred Henry, 1912, 1949
  - Sturtevant, Russell, 1934
  - Suffield School, March 24, 1930
  - Sumbardo, A.H., March 19, 1926
  - Summers, Meade, Undated
  - Sumption, Lavon, 1956
  - Sutton, T.S., July 25, 1935
  - Swain, Ella W., October, 1928
  - Sweitzer, Ralph W., May, 1932
  - Sykes, Geoffrey, 1952
  - Tabacoff, Iv.I., 1934
  - Tallent, Violet K., 1930
  - Talmadge, Harry J., September 18, 1931
  - Tang, Sigrid, December 5, 1938
  - Tar Products Corporation, 1932
  - Taylor, George E., December 12, 1929
  - Taylor, J.C., March, 1953
  - Taylor, Lewis W., 1932, 1964-1965
  - Teisen, Aase, March 5, 1930
  - TenBroeck, Carl, 1930-1932
  - Ten Eyck, Peter G., 1932-1933
  - Termohlen, W.D., 1930, 1936
  - Terry, B.T., 1908
  - Thermal Syndicate Ltd., 1924-1926
  - Third International Congress of Eugenics, April 5, 1932
  - Third Pan-American Scientific Congress, July 19, 1924
  - Thomas, Arthur H., Co., 1924-1931
  - Thomas, Charles C., 1928
  - Thompson, A.A., 1928-1931
  - Thompson, George E., January 30, 1926
  - Thompson, Moreland, 1941-1952
  - Thompson, R.B., January 9, 1928
    See: Martin, J Holmes, in:
  - Thompson, W. Robert, January 16, 1964
  - Thompson, Willard C., 1927-1930
  - Thomson, A.C., July 14, 1936
  - Thone, Frank, August 10, 1949
  - Thornton, Charles A., November 27, 1935
  - Thornton, John & Company, 1930
  - Tiffin, Mrs. Kenneth C., 1941-1942
  - Tillson, A.E., April, 1932
  - Titani, Koiti, June 18, 1966
  - Tobias, J. Carroll, 1926
  - Tompkins, Pendleton, October, 1949
  - Toor, Cecil J., December 6, 1933
  - Torrey, Harry Beal, November 25, 1926
  - Treadway, Allen T., March 6, 1934
  - Tufts, Leonard, 1933-1935
  - Turner, Charles W., 1925-1928
    See also: American Association of Anatomists. Symposium, in:
  - Turton, William, 1930
  - Umbaugh, R.E., June 6, 1941
  - Underbjerg, Gravers K.L., 1940-1941
  - Union of American Biological Societies, October 12, 1923
  - Universal Products Sales Company, September 21, 1927
  - Unknown, Undated
  - Upp, Charles W., 1930-1931
  - Vandenburg, Nell, 1924-1933
  - Vandevort, John, December 11, 1928
  - Van Roekel, Henry, 1930-1955
    See also: Inbred Chickens, in:
  - Van Wert, J.S., 1952
  - Vickers, G.S., 1926
  - Viets, Paul W., 1923-1925
  - Vischer, Peter, January, 1965
  - Vitamin Research Laboratories, Undated
  - Vopelius, Oswalt, 1932, 1947
  - Wachtel, Irwin J., 1941-1952
  - Walford, Stephen M., 1949-1952
  - Wallace, Henry A., 1928-1937
  - Wallace, Henry B., 1937-1952, 1963
  - Walsh, David I., May 3, 1943
  - Warner, David E., 1930-1936
  - Warner, G.A., 1924-1927
  - Warren, Don Cameron, 1923-1935, 1964
  - Warren, T.R., January 21, 1933
  - Washbon, W.E., March 27, 1950
  - Waterman, A.J., February 14, 1928
  - Waters, N.F., 1932-1937
  - Waugh, G.L., 1930
  - Waverly Press, Inc., December 30, 1926
  - Weaver, Earl, November 25, 1929
  - Weaver, H.F., January 7, 1935
  - Weaver, L.E., November 20, 1933
  - Weed, John H., November 20, 1928
  - Weeks, Wilfred D., Undated
  - Weidner, Charles H., 1942-1943
  - Weinman, I., December 6, 1928
  - Welch, W. M., Scientific Company, May 15, 1928
  - Wendler, Henry G., January 12, 1955
  - Wentworth, Edward Norris, November 6, 1927
  - Whaley, W. Gordon, August 5, 1949
  - Whipple, Clayton E., November 27, 1937
  - White, Frank B., August, 1927
  - White, G.C., July, 1932
  - Whitelock, William M.E., 1928-1929
  - Whiting, P.W., November 10, 1929
  - Whitney, D.D., Undated
  - Whitney, F.P., 1926
  - Whitney, Leon F., 1928-1929
  - Whittinghill, Maurice, May 20, 1942
  - Wicks, Stanton D., September 25, 1935
  - Wilby, Giles H., February 28, 1927
  - Wilcox, Philip A., May, 1928
  - Wilcox, T.H., July 24, 1935
  - Wildman, W.E., February 16, 1951
  - Wiley, William H., October 26, 1949
  - Wilhelm G., Ottmar, July, 1929
  - Wilhjelm, K.H., 1929-1935
  - Wilkins, Harold T., 1925
  - Wilkins, S.D., 1927-1928
  - Wilkinson, J.F., 1932
  - Willard, H.S., April, 1932
  - Willer, Adolf, May 29, 1929
  - Willet, N.L., January 3, 1925
  - Willett, E.L., 1952-1953
  - Williams, B.M., April 24, 1931
  - William, Hubert J., February 8, 1926
  - Williams, Richard E., 1932-1934
  - Williams, Samuel B., Jr., May, 1932
  - Williams, W.W., 1927-1930
  - Williams College Library, October, 1934
  - Williams and Wilkins Company, 1927-1928
  - Williamstown, Mass., Town of, February 26, 1927
  - Wilson, Mrs. Bessie G., October 30, 1950
  - Wilson, Edwin Bidwell, 1905, 1930
  - Wilson, J. W., Glass Company, Inc., November, 1931
  - Wilson, J. Walter, 1948
  - Wilson, Logan T., August 30, 1935
  - Wilson, Wilbor O., 1966
  - Wing, Henry H., 1932-1934
  - Wintermeyer, W.E., June 23, 1927
  - Winton, Berley, September 29, 1948
  - Wiper, Harold, March 31, 1958
  - Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology, 1911-1929
  - Witschi, Emil, Undated
  - Wixon, D.P., October 26, 1925
  - Wohnus, J.F., 1954-1955
  - Wood, Ebenezer, September 5, 1929
  - Wood, H. Curtis, Jr., November 7, 1949
  - Wood, W.F., Jr., January 19, 1927
  - Woodley, W.H., 1932
  - Woodward, Harold O., February 2, 1952
  - Woolley, George Walter, June 24, 1941
  - Worden, H.W., 1931
  - Wortman, L.S., February, 1926
  - Wright, Sewall, 1932-1937
  - Wylie, C.E., 1932
  - Yapp, W.W., Undated
  - Zavitz, R.W., February 18, 1926
  - Zehner, L.A., November 2, 1955
  - Zeiss, Carl, Inc., December 16, 1926
  - Zich, Gerald E., 1949-1950
  - Zigler, Edward, 1967
  - Zimmerli, A., 1925-1926
  - Zion's Cooperative Mercantile Institution, November, 1931
  - Zirkle, Conway, November 5, 1951
  - Zucker, Theodore F., 1950
  - Zumbro, P.B., 1932, 1936
- Series II. Articles and Notes, 1910-1966
  - Aged whites
  - Analysis of a hen's egg record (no.1)
  - Applied genetics-directed evolution #1
  - Applied genetics-directed evolution #2
  - Applied genetics-directed evolution #3
  - Applied genetics: more food from fewer animals
  - Art of progeny test breeding
  - Bearing of the genotype of extreme variants on selection
  - Better babies-overpopulation #1
  - Better babies-overpopulation #2
  - Bibliography
  - Biology in agriculture, May 2, 1929
    Lecture, Mount Holyoke College.
  - BioScience, Dec. 1966
    Articles on population growth, with notes.
  - Breeder's problem
  - Breeding for egg production
  - Breeding for large size in the mouse
    A progress report based on fifty-four generations of family selection.
  - Breeding experiments with mice
  - Breeding for improvement
  - Breeding larger mice
  - Breeding policies and average production
  - Breeding poultry for profit
  - Breeding for profitable dairy cattle
  - Breeding records-cattle #1
  - Breeding records-cattle #2
  - Breeding records-cattle #3
  - Breeding records-cattle #4
  - Breeding records-cattle #5
  - Breeding records-cattle #6
  - Breeding records-cattle #7
  - Breeding records-cattle #8
  - Breeding records-cattle #9
  - Breeding records-cattle #10
  - Breeding records-cattle #11
  - Breeding records-cattle #12
  - Breeding records-cattle #13
  - Breeding records-cattle #14
  - Breeding records-cattle #15
  - Breeding records-cattle #16
  - Breeding records-cattle #17
  - Breeding records-cattle #18
  - Breeding records-cattle #19
  - Breeding records-cattle #20
  - Breeding records-mice #1
  - Breeding records-mice #2
  - Breeding records-mice #3
  - Breeding records-mice #4
  - Breeding records-mice #5
  - Breeding records-mice #6
  - Breeding records-pedigree control-chickens #1
  - Breeding records-pedigree control-chickens #2
  - Breeding records-pedigree control-Rhode Island reds
  - Breeding records-poultry #1
  - Breeding records-poultry #2
  - Breeding records-poultry #3
  - Breeding records-poultry #4
  - Breeding records-poultry #5
  - Breeding records-poultry #6
  - Breeding records-poultry #7
  - Breeding records-poultry #8
  - Breeding records-poultry #9
  - Breeding records-poultry #10
  - Breeding records-poultry #11
  - Breeding records-poultry #12
  - Breeding records-poultry #13
  - Breeding records-poultry #14
  - Breeding records-poultry #15
  - Breeding records-poultry #16
  - Breeding records-poultry #17
  - Breeding records-poultry #18
  - Breeding records-poultry #19
  - Breeding records-poultry #20
  - Breeding records-poultry #21
  - Breeding records-poultry #22
  - Breeding records-poultry #23
  - Breeding records-poultry #24
  - Breeding records-poultry #25
  - Breeding records-poultry #26
  - Breeding records-poultry #27
  - Breeding records-poultry #28
  - Breeding records-poultry #29
  - Breeding records-poultry #30